{
    "subject": "resource/Man_in_the_Moon_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film 'Man in the Moon' is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9859514236450195,
            "question": "Is 'Man in the Moon' an English-language film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8699724674224854,
            "question": "What language was the film 'Man in the Moon' filmed in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8262602686882019,
            "question": "Is there a dubbed version of 'Man in the Moon' in any languages other than English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8106712698936462,
            "question": "Is there a different language spoken besides English in 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6922038197517395,
            "question": "What is the primary language used in 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6418919563293457,
            "question": "In which language can 'Man in the Moon' be understood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6398000717163086,
            "question": "What language would subtitles be provided in for viewers who don't speak English and are watching 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6129212379455566,
            "question": "If you want to watch 'Man in the Moon', do you need to know another language besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6080477833747864,
            "question": "Would someone who speaks English be able to watch and understand 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6043972969055176,
            "question": "Does 'Man in the Moon' feature dialogue primarily in English?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film 'Man in the Moon' is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5980_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would someone who speaks English be able to watch and understand 'Man in the Moon'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5980_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you want to watch 'Man in the Moon', do you need to know another language besides English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5980_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language would subtitles be provided in for viewers who don't speak English and are watching 'Man in the Moon'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5980_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5980_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer indicates that the triple \"The language of the film 'Man in the Moon' is English\" is supported by the documents. The relevant sentence from document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5980/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt` states:\n\n\"Tonight's movie is the 1991 coming-of-age drama, 'The Man in the Moon.'\"\n\nThere is no specific information about the language of the film in any of the documents. However, since there are multiple references to English-language films and Hollywood releases, it can be inferred that \"English\" is likely the dominant language used in this context. Therefore, the response is positive."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe document states that \"The Man in the Moon\" stars actors speaking English and it was directed by Robert Mulligan, strongly implying the movie's primary language is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}